Akshay More

Pune, Maharashtra, India



akshaymorejl04@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/akshaymore2018



https://akshaymore2018.github.io/

Summary

A fan of preparation and established fundamentals, because they give a better understanding of which rules to break, and which rules to think twice about. Expert in strategic and tactical planning. Knowledgeable about programming paradigms, design patterns, rendering pipeline stages, and optimization techniques. Experienced in game development life cycle. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Computer Science from MIT Academy of Engineering, Pune.

Experience



S Junior Programmer

Sumo Digital Ltd

Aug 2020 - Present (3 months +)

1) Unannounced Project

[C++] [UE4] [3D]

- Working as a gameplay programmer for the project.

Trainee Programmer

Sumo Digital Ltd

Aug 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year)

1) Spyder

[C++] [UE4] [3D] [iOS] [macOS] [TVOS] [Apple Arcade]

- Worked on its DLC.
- Created a gameplay mechanic to be used by designers to set up micro-mission in the game for the player.
- Apple Game Center Achievements and Leaderboards for iOS, macOS and tvOS
- DLC related UI
- Fixed a lot of bugs to ensure stable build.

2) Unannounced Project

[C++] [UE4] [3D] [PC] [PS4] [Xbox] [Switch]

- I was responsible for the implementation of all the power ups.
- I also programmed some of the Interact-able game objects and the physics involved with them.
- Hooking up and playing of the SFXs (Wwise) and VFXs.
- Was also responsible for implementation of one Game Mode.
- Also worked on game UI.
- Bug fixes.

Game Programmer

Rendered Ideas

Dec 2017 - Mar 2019 (1 year 4 months)

1) Jungle Adventures 3:

[Java] [Android] [Google Play]

- Programmed enemies and other game play mechanics.
- Programmed majority of the bosses.
- Programmed majority of the UI.

2) Virtual Life Interactive:

[Java] [Android] [Google Play]

- Was the lead programmer on this and programmed the entire game.
- Developed the custom game script and created tools to help designers set up the in-game content.
- Programmed the entire UI.

Education



MIT Academy of Engineering, Pune

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science 2013 - 2017



Kendriya Vidyalaya

High School Diploma, Mathematics and Computer Science

Skills

C++ • Game Development • Design Patterns • Algorithms • OpenGL • Visual Studio 2017 • Simple and Fast Multimedia Library (SFML) • Unreal Engine 4 • Perforce • Wwise